原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
翻译     累
校对     累
时间轴     西·查    想念Gallifrey的Wholock
后期     累
总监     累
我需要帮忙
I need a favor.
我在这里最后一天了  我才不陪你去大街购物
I'm not spending my last day here watching you shop on Main Street.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
杰米
Jamie.
我有麻烦了
I'm in trouble.
-孩子的父亲是谁  -不关你的事
- Who's the father? - That's none of your business.
这必须关我的事啊
It is absolutely my business--
不  这是我的事
No, it's my business!
有什么区别呢
What difference does it make?
我先去打听一下
Let me go figure this out.
你是艾伦吗
Are you Ellen?
是的
I am.
我们之前通过电话
We spoke on the phone.
你是白人啊
You're white.
比林斯有计划生育部门
There's a Planned Parenthood in Billings.
-带她去那儿吧  -不行
- Take her there. - I can't.
到时候大家就都知道了
Everyone will know.
那是匿名的  没人会知道的
It's anonymous. Nobody will know.
所有人都会知道
Everyone will know.
听着
Listen.
你们最好还是别在这里做
You don't want to do this here.
这家诊所对堕胎患者的要求
A requirement of patients receiving an abortion
是绝育手术
at this clinic is sterilization.
明白
Understood.
没事吧
Is it okay?
嗯  没事
Yeah. It's okay.
黄石
第三季  第五集
你去哪儿了
Where've you been?
进城了
Went to town.
你验孕了吗
Did you get the test?
嗯  阴性
Yeah. It was negative.
那你为什么这么难过
Why do you look so sad?
我们到此为止吧
We shouldn't do this anymore.
你没事吧
You okay?
不好的梦
Bad dream.
不好的回忆
Bad memory.
那是很难受
Those are worse.
是啊
Yeah.
聊聊吗
You wanna talk?
不了
No.
这次就算了
Not this one.
说说呗
Tell me anyway.
我一生中做了两个基于恐惧的决定
I've made two decisions in my life based on fear.
这两个决定让我付出了一切
And they cost me everything.
不至于
Not everything.
重复我说的话
Repeat after me:
我郑重发誓我会支持
I do solemnly swear that I will support,
保护和维护美国
protect, and uphold the Constitution of the United States
以及蒙大拿州宪法
and the Constitution of the State of Montana.
我郑重宣誓我会支持  保护
I do solemnly swear that I will support, protect,
和维护美国
and uphold the Constitution of the United States
以及蒙大拿州宪法
and the Constitution of the State of Montana.
我将忠诚地履行我的职责
And that I will discharge the duties of my office with fidelity,
上帝保佑我
so help me God.
我将忠诚地履行我的职责
And that I will discharge the duties of my office with fidelity,
上帝保佑我
so help me God.
最后那部分再说一遍
Say that last part again.
我将忠诚地履行我的职责
And that I will discharge the duties of my office with Fidelity.
上帝保佑你
So help you, God.
上帝保佑我
So help me God.
-恭喜你  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
-恭喜你  杰米  -谢谢
- Congratulations, Jamie. - Thank you.
他现在是你的人了
He's all yours, now.
费了这么大的劲  终于得偿所愿了
We took the long way to get here, but here we are.
得偿所愿了
Here we are.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
我会帮你熟悉一下
I'll help you with your transition
然后我要打一年高尔夫球
then I'm playing golf for a year.
谢谢你  州长
Well, thank you, Governor.
谢谢你父亲吧
Thank your father.
我知道我为什么会在这里
I know why I'm here.
并不是因为他
And it wasn't him.
来  我带你去你的办公室
Come on. I'll show you your office.
哈斯克尔治安官  一号线
Sheriff Haskell, line one.
喂
Yeah?
你认识去埃米格兰的博伊德·纳尔逊吗
You know Boyd Nelson, out toward Emigrant?
-听说过  -他自杀了
- I know of him. - Committed suicide.
来他的农场找我
Meet me at his ranch.
我去干什么
What's that got to do with my office?
到时候你就知道了
You'll see.
他留了遗书吗
He leave a note?
算是吧
Sort of.
取消抵押赎回权通知
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
他有孩子吧
He's got kids, don't he?
两个
He's got two of them.
这些也归银行吗
Bank take those, too?
一旦法医
Well, soon as the Medical Examiner
签发死亡证明  凯斯
releases a death certificate, Kayce,
银行就会拿走一切
bank takes everything.
要是它们不在了  就拿不走了
Can't take them if they're not here.
我们把它们圈起来
What if we round them up,
运到比林斯去卖吧
and take them down to Billings and put them in a sale?
给那些孩子弄点生活费
Give those kids some sort of chance at life.
这合法吗
Is that legal?
不  不合法
Hell, no, it's ain't legal.
你刚当牲畜委员会委员
And I'm not so sure that violating probate law
就违反遗嘱认证法  不好吧
should be your first act as Livestock Commissioner, either.
嗯
Yeah.
如果我要违反  你打算怎么办
What if it was, though, where would you stand on it?
他是我表兄弟  凯斯  你说我怎么办
He was my cousin, Kayce. That's where I stand.
如果你打算动手  我就装作没看见
If you wanna do it I'll look away,
但如果银行发现  你就麻烦了
but if the bank finds out you are up to your neck in trouble.
我和我爸谈谈
I need to talk to my father.
好的
All right.
我们必须要走吗
Do we have to go?
是的  你爸爸得在城里工作
Yeah, your dad's gotta work in the city.
城里太操蛋了
The city sucks ass.
什么玩意
Sucks what?
你这话在哪学的
Hey, where are you learning this stuff?
瞧瞧那只蜘蛛  真他妈大
Jesus, look at the size of that fucking spider.
那他妈是只大蟾蜍
That is a big-ass toad.
操  你可以给那玩意装个鞍
Shit, you could saddle that sumbitch,
骑着它回工棚了
and ride his fucking ass back to the barn.
我知道了
Well, I think I know.
里普  我们的帐篷先别收了吧
Hey, Rip, can you leave our tent up?
今年夏天我想让泰特多来这里玩玩
I want to get Tate out here as much as I can this summer.
没问题  女士
Yes, ma'am, I can do that.
谢谢
Thanks.
这是最后的了
These are the last ones.
杰克  伊桑  把驮马拉回来
Jake, Ethan, drag them pack horses back.
劳埃德  给他们俩找两匹温顺的马
Lloyd, find something gentle for them two.
提特  给那匹黄马  还有白马套上马鞍
Teeter, let's saddle that yellow horse and the white horse.
莱恩  科尔比  我们负责围栏
Ryan, Colby? We're running the fence.
你最近很难找啊
You've become a very difficult man to get a hold of.
是的  我定了个新规则
Yeah, well, I have this new rule:
我只在没有信号的地方带手机
I only carry my phone in places with no service.
否则就把手机放在厨房的柜台上
Otherwise that son of a bitch stays on the kitchen counter.
我酸了
Well, I envy you that luxury.
是时候讨论我们的新问题了
I thought it was time we discuss our new problem.
嗯
Yeah.
问题似乎不会自行消失  对吧
Doesn't seem to be going away on its own, does it?
这个不会
Not this one.
联邦航空局已经批准了你的一部分土地
The FAA has approved a portion of your land
作为机场的位置  我相信你已经知道了
as the airport location, as I'm sure you're aware.
州政府会提出条件  你拒绝后
The state will make an offer and after you refuse...
检察长负责处理本州的征用权案件
The Attorney General handles eminent domain cases for the state,
这点我并不担心
and I'm not concerned with that office anymore.
这是州长的决定
It's the Governor's decision.
这点我也不担心
I'm not worried about that office either.
四千份工作机会啊  约翰
It's four thousand jobs, John.
影响可不小
In a state where that makes a difference.
不支持的话  她这州长就干不下去了
Not supporting this will cost her the office.
你居然会反对  汤姆
Well, I'm surprised you're against it, Tom.
机场就在你的赌场旁边
An airport right down the street from your casino,
虽然我不是酒店经理
I'm no hotel manager,
但这应该是件好事吧
but that sounds like a good thing to me.
我和赌场有一些所有权的问题
I have some ownership issues with the casino property.
我可不会帮你摆平
Well, I'm not going to help you with the problem
妨碍你建赌场的问题
that prevents you from building a casino.
赌场和机场最好一个都别建
I don't want a casino any more than I want an airport.
我也不希望看到别人建赌场
I don't really want another casino either.
这是对于印第安人收入来源的
It's an insulting-- and wickedly ironic--
一种侮辱  极其的讽刺
revenue stream for an Indian Nation.
这是为了达到目标的手段
It is a means to an end
最后的目标就是这个山谷
and that end is this valley looking like it did
完全没有白人留下的痕迹
before a white man stepped foot on it.
我们的目标一致  但原因截然不同
We want the same thing for very different reasons.
我们可以回头再战
And we can have our fight later,
但如果他们在这里建一座城市
but we'll have nothing to fight over
我们就没有什么可争的了
if they build a city here.
我同意
Well, I agree with you on that.
你知道我的商业背景
You know my business background.
一个项目绝不是靠一场战争就能决定是否推进的
It's never one fight that determines if a project moves forward.
这是战斗的积累
It's an accumulation of fights.
公司讨厌"复杂"
Corporations hate "Complicated".
他们要看到回报
And they need to see a return.
他们钱和人都不缺
They have the money. They have the manpower.
他们有权有势
They have the influence and the reach,
但公司缺的是时间
but the one thing corporations never have is time.
这是他们唯一的敌人
It's their only enemy.
我们要利用时间打败他们
And that's how we beat them.
我们给他们提供一些耗费时间的东西
We give them a dozen things that take time.
我这里有一个善于寻找这些东西的人
Now, I have someone with a reputation of finding those things.
她找到以后  可以无情地交给公司
And she is merciless when she's found them.
我正好也有一个人选
Well... I have one of those, too.
我知道
I'm aware.
这就是我来这里的原因  她们应该见个面
That's why I'm here. I think they should meet.
两个人商量一下
Put their heads together.
谁知道她们能搞出什么花样呢
Then who knows what mischief they'll come up with together.
我得提醒一下你
I'm just warning you:
我的人可不留后路的
this genie does not go back in the bottle.
我的人也一样
Neither does mine.
先交易员一步
Get in front of the trader.
嗯  等等
Right. Wait.
我在看
I'm watching.
就现在  135点卖30万
Now. Three hundred-thousand at one thirty-five.
他买了就告诉我
Tell me when he takes.
卖空我的股票
Short my fucking stock...
买了吗  太好了
Bought? Yes!
舒服了吧  红发小贱人
Take that you little red-headed shit.
喂
Yeah.
什么
What?
又跌了一点
Another point?
我要去钓鱼啊
I'm trying to go fucking fishing!
操了
God!
操
为什么我们不和他们一起走
Why can't we ride with them?
因为那条路太难走了
'Cause that's a pretty rough haul.
老蓝色牛仔裤心中装不下大山了
Old Blue Jeans, he ain't got any more mountains in him.
蓝色牛仔裤是谁
Who's Blue Jeans?
蓝色牛仔裤是你要骑的马
Blue Jeans is the horse you're gonna be ridin'.
它和你爸爸的岁数差不多大
He's almost as old as your daddy.
我还记得你爸爸以前到处乱跑
In fact, I can remember when your daddy used to run
还要骑那匹傻...
all over hell and gone on that son of a...
好马
Son of a gun.
你们这些牧民别在他面前说脏话了
The pirate mouth on that kid needs no help from you wranglers.
-你们能  -对不起
- If y'all could just... - Sorry.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我孩子说脏话其实也不怪你
It's not your responsibility what my kid says.
我们在他面前会注意言辞的
We'll try and really watch what we say around him.
谢谢
I'd appreciate it.
咚咚
Knock knock.
谁啊
Who's there?
欧洲
Europe.
哪个欧洲
Europe, who?
是你这个混蛋
No, you're a poo!
算了  他这是天生的
Nope. It's just in him.
但他笑得很开心啊  不是吗
He's laughing, though, ain't he?
是的
Yeah, he is.
这个可教不来
You can't teach that.
什么教不来
Teach what?
韧性
Toughness.
人一生下来  不是柳树就是橡树
You're either born a willow or you're born an oak.
就这么简单
That's all there is to it.
你们俩准备好了吗
You two ready?
好了
Ready ready.
什么鬼
What in the...
它们是从公园溜进来的吗
You think they wandered in from the park?
不是  那边围栏很多的
Nah, there's too many fences.
这群狗娘养的是谁
Who are these son of a bitches here?
去看看
Come on. Let's go.
运动俱乐部还养上野牛了
Sporting Club running buffalo now?
运动俱乐部啥也不弄了
Sporting Club ain't running shit no more.
好吧  那些是谁的牛
Yell, well, whose are those, then?
这不重要  反正不是你们的
Don't matter, as long as they're not yours.
你们有许可证吗
You got permission to run them things here?
没有  我今天刚决定在农场养点野牛
No, I just decided today I'd run some buffalo
也没什么特殊的原因
across a field for no reason.
我的牛要是因为那些破玩意
Yeah, well, I don't want my cattle getting brucellosis
染上布鲁氏菌病就不好了
from them fucking things.
别让你的牛穿过围栏就行了
Keep your cattle on your side of the fence.
告诉你的马仔
You oughta tell your boy
和我说话的时候注意点
to watch the bass in his voice when he speaks to me.
马仔
Boy?
信不信我爆了你的头
I'll blow your shit-for-brains all over this field.
有本事就试试
Then fucking do it.
保护区探员  牲畜委员会
Reserve agent, Livestock Association.
不许动  不然我就开枪了
I will shoot you where you stand.
把手枪放下
Put that fucking pistol down.
保护区探员
Reserve agent?
达顿还在那骗人呢
Duttons are still running that scam?
我们不认识你
We don't know you.
的确  但你们老板认识
You wouldn't. But your boss does.
告诉他韦德·莫罗向他问好
Tell him Wade Morrow said hello.
我相信我们还会见面的
We'll see each other again, I'm sure.
你还是祈祷咱俩再也不见吧
You better hope I never see you again.
下次和我来个公平的对决
Next time, fight me fair.
操  现在就来啊
Shit, I'll fight you fair.
下马
Get off your horse.
下次再说吧
We'll save that for a rainy day.
我需要它们没有感染布鲁氏菌病的证据
I need proof those are brucellosis free.
如果你够爷们的话  就来拿吧
If you're man enough, come and get it.
走吧
Come on.
他们为什么要把野牛留在这里
Why would they leave buffalo out here?
它们会把围栏毁掉的
They're gonna tear this fence to pieces.
这就是为什么
That's why.
现在5点了
You know, it's 5 o'clock.
你不应该在河里吗
Shouldn't you be in a river somewhere?
威士忌  加冰
Bulleit. Rocks.
我最喜欢的就是在河里钓鱼
There's nothing I love more than to be on the river,
但我来这里是想弄清楚
but instead, I'm here trying to figure out
你为什么要摸老虎屁股
why you are poking a grizzly.
你钓到鱼以后  并不会留着
You don't keep them when you catch them.
没错
No.
你会把鱼扔回河里
You throw them back.
是的
Yes.
你要是吃了  还可以得到我的尊重
I could respect you if you ate them.
这样我比较能理解一点
That makes sense to me.
但是鳟鱼一整天要经历的破事
But of all the shit a trout has to go through in a day...
老鹰想吃掉它
eagles trying to eat them,
浣熊想吃掉它
raccoons trying to eat them,
水獭  鱼鹰  大鱼  鹰
otters, ospreys, bigger fish, hawks.
它还要思考漂浮的死昆虫身上
It also has to wonder if every floating dead insect
有没有钩子  因为你觉得它
has a fucking hook in it because you think it
为了生命和你斗智斗勇
fighting you for its life...
很有趣
Is fun.
钩子不会弄疼鱼
It doesn't hurt the fish.
鱼不像其他动物那样处理疼痛
They don't process pain the way other animals do--
鱼素者是这么跟你说的吗
What fucking pescatarian told you that, huh?
这个星球上有一种脊椎动物
It is fascinating that the one vertebrate
不依赖疼痛作为生存手段
on this planet that doesn't rely on pain as a survival device
你就喜欢钩住它们的嘴  好棒棒哦
is the one that you like to hook in the fucking mouth.
说实话  鱼疼不疼关我屁事
To be honest, I could give a shit if it hurts the fish.
我不喜欢鱼的味道  所以我把它们扔回去了
I don't like the way it tastes. That's why I throw them back.
你为什么一开始不说呢
Well, why didn't you say that in the first place, huh?
那我就懂了呀
That I understand.
舒瓦茨和梅耶公司正在卖空我们的股票
Schwartz and Meyer shorting our stock
就像恐怖分子炸地铁一样
is like a terrorist bombing a subway.
这样无法阻止地铁
It doesn't stop the subways
也不会破坏地铁服务的城市
and it doesn't destroy the city the subway serves.
只是伤害了一些人
It just hurts some people,
而且并非是你想伤害的人
and not the people you want to hurt.
但这样会让你想伤害的人
But it does make the people you want to hurt
以牙还牙
want to hurt you back.
你想以牙还牙
You going to try and hurt me back,
这就是你想说的吗
is that what you're trying to say?
这种事我经历过很多次了  伙计
Because I have been down this road many, many times before, buddy.
很可惜  尝试过的人都死了
And no one who tried it is alive to tell you
他们没办法告诉你效果有多差了
how poorly that worked out for them.
什么意思  你是说如果我找你算账
What, are you saying you're going to hire a fucking hitman
你就要雇杀手干掉我吗
to come after me if I come after you?
我们可以买下十五个舒瓦茨和梅耶公司
We could buy Schwartz and Meyer fifteen times over.
那片土地不是你家族的遗产
That land is not your family's legacy.
这是一个可以继续增值的遗迹
It is a relic that will continue to appreciate
直到你的家人负担不起
until your family can no longer afford it
然后你们就会失去它
and then you will lose it.
财富是唯一的遗产  你知道的
Wealth is the only legacy left, and you know it.
和我们作对  你就会输掉所有的钱
Fight us and you'll lose all your money
还有土地
and you lose the land.
你也可以做个聪明的女商人
Or be the smart business woman you are
与我们达成协议  为你的家庭创造真正的遗产
and make us a deal that creates a real legacy for your family.
五六亿的遗产
Five, six hundred-million dollars.
世代的财富
Generational wealth.
你说的我都同意  罗尔克
I agree on all fronts, Roarke.
真的
I do.
我向上帝祈祷他愿意这么做
And I wish to God that he would do that,
但他不会的
but he won't.
所以我们战斗吧
So, we fight.
你把自己封在了阿拉莫  贝丝
You're sealing yourself into the Alamo, Beth.
这些人也是只杀不俘的
And these guys won't take prisoners either.
我很期待
I look forward to it.
别卖空我的股票  求你了
Stop shorting my fucking stock, please.
那你别让我轻易得逞啊
Well, stop making it so fucking easy.
你能在盘后交易吗
Could you at least do it in after hours trading
让我好好钓个鱼呗
so I can fucking fish?
这没问题
Well, that I can do.
我可以在盘后卖空你的股票
I will short your stock in after-hours trading
让你可以安心折磨鳟鱼
so you can torture trout.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
贝丝  你自以为准备好了
You think you're up for this fight, Beth.
但你其实大错特错
You have no idea how wrong you are.
彼此彼此
Well, right back at you.
你是拖车公园
You are the trailer park.
我是龙卷风
I am the tornado.
第一天上任感觉如何
How was your first day?
博伊德·纳尔逊死了
Boyd Nelson died.
饲马人
The horse breeder?
其实我不认识他
I didn't really know him.
他是个梦想家
He was a dreamer.
那些梦想没有实现  他变成了
When those dreams didn't come true he became...
他变得很易怒
He was an angry, angry guy.
留置权人取消了牧场的抵押赎回权
The lien-holder's foreclosing on his ranch.
他唯一有价值的东西
Only thing he has worth anything
是300匹左右的母马  还有些马驹
is about 300 brood mares, some babies.
我想着把它们圈起来
I was thinking maybe I could round them up,
送到比林斯卖了
take them down to Billings, put them in a sale.
帮帮他的家人
Try to help his family out.
前提是他家值得我这么做
That is, if it's a family worth doing it for.
他妻子是个好女人
His wife's a good woman.
反正博伊德配不上她
Better than Boyd deserved, that's for sure.
她真是可惜了
I'm sorry for her.
如果银行发现的话  会有点风险
There's a bit of a risk, if the bank were to find out.
银行你就不用管了
Bank's not your problem.
你要在意的是民众
Your problem is the people.
你的工作就是为他们着想
Do what's best for them. That's the job.
你是说我应该帮他们吗
You saying I should do it?
我什么也没说  这不是我要做的决定
Not saying anything. Not my decision to make.
要是行动的话
Well, if do,
那我需要你的帮助
I'm gonna need your help.
只要你下了决定  我肯定会全力帮你的
Once you make the decision, I'll do whatever you want.
伙计们  谢谢你们的帮助
Fellas, thanks for helping out.
你打算怎么做
How do you plan on doing this?
里普  你知道怎么办
Rip, have you figured out how to do this
才能不被马群践踏吗
without all of us getting trampled?
我们想到的最好的办法是"管它呢"
Best we came up with sir is like, "fuck it", you know?
我们尽快上去
Let's get up there fast as we can
把那些马赶下山
and just chase those sons of bitches down the mountain.
管它呢
Fuck it.
这也是你的计划吗  "管它呢"
That's your plan, too? Fuck it?
不管我们怎么做  场面都不会好看
It's gonna be a shit show no matter what we do.
还不如快一点
May as well do it fast.
减少出错的时间
Less time for things to go wrong.
你的逻辑有缺陷  儿子
Your logic is so flawed, son, it...
操  我还真挑不出理来
Hell, it almost makes sense.
真棒
Great.
好吧
All right.
管它呢
Fuck it.
我以为肯定有人要去医院了呢
I thought for sure someone was going to the hospital.
我以为有人要死了呢
I thought someone was dying.
我有点想上山再来一次
You know, I've got half a mind to run up that hill and do it again.
检察长在三号线
Attorney General on line three.
检察长
Attorney general?
三号线
Line three.
是斯图尔特检察长还是检察长当选人里德啊
Is this AG Stewart or AG elect Reid?
我是新任命的达顿检察长
It's newly appointed AG Dutton.
杰米
Jamie?
我觉得我应该亲口告诉你
I just thought you should hear from me directly,
作为该州最高执法官员
as the highest law enforcement officer in the state,
如果你有任何尚未解决的问题需要解决
that my office is available for anything that you might need.
我会尽最大的努力帮你解决
If there are any unresolved issues that need resolving.
你能想到什么问题吗  兰迪
Can you think of anything, Randy?
不
No.
没有尚未解决的问题
No, there's no unresolved issues.
那就好
I'm glad to hear it.
谁来当牲畜委员会委员
Who'll be the new Livestock Commissioner?
凯斯
Kayce.
你是怎么办到的  杰米
How in the hell did you manage all of this, Jamie?
我也想问自己同样的问题
You know, I ask myself that same question.
老实说  兰迪
To be honest with you, Randy,
可能是我太想要了
I think I just willed it to happen.
如果你有什么想要的  请告诉我
Let me know if there's something I can will for you.
好的
Will do.
不客气
You're welcome.
谢谢
Thank you.
随时效劳
Any time.
冠军拍卖行
你还真没开玩笑
You weren't kidding.
那些是什么
What are they?
妈妈和孩子们
Mamas and babies.
你能把它们都卖掉吗
Think you can move them all?
你愿意打包卖吗
Will you sell them as a package?
那样更好
I prefer it.
我一个电话就能打包卖掉三百匹
Hell, I can sell three hundred in a package with a phone call.
你们怎么样
How y'all doing?
我们爸爸死了  你觉得呢
Our dad died. How do you think we're doing?
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
大家都很遗憾  也没什么区别
Everybody's sorry. And it don't make no difference.
纳尔逊太太呢
Mrs. Nelson?
她在里面
She's inside.
谢谢
Thank you.
妈呀  太烫了
Oh, my word, this is hot.
戴着烤箱手套都不管用
It's burning right through these oven mitts.
卡罗琳  这是凯斯·达顿
Carolyn, this is Kayce Dutton.
-纳尔逊太太  -谢谢
- Mrs. Nelson... - Thank you.
你卖了多少钱
How much did you get for them?
一万六多一点
A little over sixteen thousand.
我也想多卖点  但是
Was hoping to get more, but...
这钱可以用来办葬礼
Should help with the funeral.
这就是葬礼
This is the funeral.
我不会花一分钱埋他的
I ain't spending a dime burying him.
就让那个懦夫自行腐烂吧
That coward can rot where he lays.
牛仔和梦想家
Cowboys and dreamers.
为什么我只爱牛仔和梦想家
Why I only love cowboys and dreamers?
我永远不会明白
I will never understand.
从初吻开始  我的人生就被他们毁了
They've put me through hell from the first kiss.
按我的尿性  我可能会再嫁一个
And knowing me, I'll probably marry another one.
土豆再烤一下吧
Let's get those potatoes back in the oven.
你是牛仔吗
You a cowboy?
是的
Yeah, I am.
我爸爸生前也是牛仔
My daddy was a cowboy.
我也要当牛仔
I'm gonna be a cowboy, too.
还不错  你没问题吧
It's not bad. You all right?
吉米  哪个铺位是你的
Which bunk is yours, Jimmy?
在后面  右边上铺
In the back in the right up top.
上铺应该是睡不了了
I don't think the top one's happening.
下铺有人吗
Anyone in the bottom bunk?
现在还真没人
At the moment, actually, no.
黄石有多少牧人
How many wranglers does the Yellowstone have?
十个还是十一个
Ten or eleven.
一般会有一两个浮动
Usually a couple floating in and out.
其中一个牧人是女孩  女人
Yeah, one of the wranglers is a girl. Woman.
算是女士吧
Lady. Kind of.
拉勒米
Laramie.
他们马上就回来了
They guys are gonna be back in a minute.
如果他们发现你们在喝他们的啤酒  他们
If they catch you drinking their beer, they're gonna--
他们怎么了  他们会怎样
They're gonna what? What are they gonna do?
我们擅自喝了你们的啤酒
We helped ourselves to your beer.
希望你们别介意
Hope you don't mind.
我们看到了  她们是你的朋友吗  吉米
Yeah, we can see. They with you, Jimmy?
这不关我的事
Yeah, this was not my idea.
又要开始玩竞技了啊
Gotta start rodeoing again.
管它呢  地球上某个地方应该是星期五晚上
Fuck it. It's Friday night somewhere.
不  今天是星期五
No, today is Friday.
现在就是星期五
It literally, right now is Friday.
那星期五就是你幸运日了
Then Friday's your lucky fucking day.
她越来越喜欢你了
She's growing on you.
才没有
She's not growing on me.
她是做了一些动作之类的
Okay, she has like a couple of moves and stuff.
她是舞蹈演员  她学过
It's kinda like... She's a dancer. She studied.
她能在哪学舞蹈啊
Where in the fuck did she study dancing?
滕斯利普的牧羊屋吗
Fucking sheeper cabin in Ten Sleep?
你太老了  跳不了舞了吗
Are you too old to dance?
就没有我这个年纪干不了的事
Ain't a damn thing I'm too old to do.
这群绕桶赛手啊
Fucking barrel racers.
你现在明白那个笑话了吗  吉米
You're getting the joke now, aren't you, Jimmy?
这么美的日落  那群蠢货真能煞风景
Only those dipshits could ruin a sunset.
该死
Goddamnit.
是吗
Is it?
我没听懂
I don't understand.
伙计  老实说我也没听懂
Yeah, honestly, man, neither do I.
不会吧  不会吧
That is shocking to me.
你们这群蠢货在干什么
What the fuck are you dipshits doing?
我早该猜到是你的
I should've known it was you.
你还不了解我嘛
By now, you sure should have.
你们在举办工棚舞会吗
You're having a barn dance or something?
嗯
Yeah.
他们在狂欢
They're cutting loose.
他们今天累得不轻
They had one hell of a day.
趁着晚上好好放松一下吧
Now it sounds like they're gonna have one hell of a night.
你今天做了件好事
It's a good thing you did today.
你违反了一条原本就不应该立法的法律
You broke a rule that shouldn't be a rule in the first place.
你这么做的理由很充分
And you did it for the right reasons.
谢谢
Thanks.
我们去凑个热闹吧
Hell, should we join 'em?
我不能去
I can't.
我无法同时成为他们的老板和朋友
I never had much luck leading men and being their friend.
说不定你可以呢
Maybe it can be different for you.
晚安  儿子
Goodnight, son.